This is a Sunlife Secure Income 15. This is
Sunlife's product that can be
used as a retirement fund, educational
fund, lifetime savings, and
can be an income continuation.  So
this is Sunlife's newest plan.
It was just launched last year.  Then
he has life insurance and a centenarian
bonus.
That's it.
So his life insurance is 200% of the
face amount.  So he's doubling down.  Then
his centenarium bonus when he
reaches the age of 80, 85, 90, 95
is 50%
of the client's total life insurance coverage, which
he can advance
without having to lose in order to get
half of his life insurance
coverage.
Then he also has lifetime
guaranteed cash benefits of 6% of the face
amount annually starting at the end of the
sixth year policy or after 6 years until
age 100, when he will
receive 6% annually.
Then living benefits.  Ah, this one has a
guaranteed cash value that he can
use for emergencies
via a policy loan.  So if there are
emergency needs, is there anything
the client can get or borrow?
Then his premium payments are manageable
.  It can be paid in installments
over 15 years.  It could be 10 years, it
could be 5 years or 3 years.
Can be annual, semi-annual or quarterly
or monthly payment through auto debit or
autocharge.  Okay.  Okay.  So the
sample I made is 1 million face amount.  So
the total life insurance coverage client
is 2 million.  And his guaranteed cash
benefit is 60,000.  This is what
Sunlife will give after 6 years,
then every year
until he is 100 years old.  Okay?  So
here is the sample I made, the
insured is 7 years old.  So, this can be from zero
age to 70 years old to 65
years old, this plan can be used.  Okay.
So all I did was say the
insured is 7 years old and the owner is
36 years old.  Okay.  So the face amount
I put in is 1 million.
His total insurance coverage is 2
million.  No, then his calculation is that
he has been in school for 1 year.
If the client wants to change it,
just do it 10 years, 5 years, 3 years later
on in the future,
it can just be recomputed.  Okay?  So because the
insured is a minor, I put a waiver of
premium upon debt or disability of the
initial owner.
How is this?  For example,
the owner is
36 years old and something happens to
him.  It's either death or disability,
having an accident or getting sick and
being diagnosed with total disability or being
truly disabled.  Unable to
work anymore.  He can no longer do
his job.  So consider that as
disability.  So that means that the
rest of the years that
the client will still pay for will be Sunlift, which will
continue.  For example,
if the plan has only been paid for 2 years, the
client is gone, and the owner is gone
for the rest of the year,
like for example, Sunlife has been paying for 13 years
until
the plan ends, then don't worry because the
benefits are still the same, okay, so at
his age, because I put in 1 million,
there is a minimum, the
example I gave here is 1 million, the
annual is 163.
The quarterly is 45,000.
So his monthly income is probably
45,000
94/3 so he's 15,000 per month because
I put in 1 million.  So this is possible up to and including
how much the
client wants.  There you go.  So these are the
main benefits of the plan.  Okay.  So when the
client or the insured child turns 8 years old
,
dividends will immediately appear.  Okay?  Sunlife has cash
available immediately.  So
those are dividends, if you don't
take them, they accumulate,
they can earn 4.50%.
So the dividends and accumulation rate
are not guaranteed because
the rate changes, sometimes every 2
years or every next uh, sometimes every 1
year it changes, but usually every
2 years there is a change,
increasing or sometimes decreasing, but here
this is the calculation that was given,
not the projected
calculation.  So there are already dividends in the first year
.  If not taken, it
accumulates.  Okay.  Then guaranteed
cash value.  This is ready cash or ready
credit that a client can borrow if they
need money in an emergency.
Clients can get up to 80% here.  So it ca
n't be 100% because the plan will be terminated
.  So only 80% can be taken.
Then that 80%,
Sunlife doesn't obligate you to
pay it immediately.  It depends on when
you pay him or return him.  But it's much
better if you return it.  He has some
interest, but not that much.
And Sunl's interest rate per anum
.  So this will help you
just in case you don't have enough money to pay
the premium or you have an emergency that
you need to pay.  'Right?
For example, you need additional
capital for your business.  You don't
need to borrow from the bank because
you can borrow with your own policy.
Okay.  Then guaranteed endowment benefit.
This is the 6% that Sunlife will give,
fixed until age 100. So 60,000 60,000
starting this year, then every year
until you reach age 100. That's it.
That's straight forward.  Directly.  Then
when he reaches 80 years old,
he can advance his life insurance
coverage by 25%.  Then if
the 85 year old is reached again, another 25%.
As long as the client has a total of 100%
of life insurance coverage,
he can advance.  Okay?  Then
what if it's not taken, it's what
he accumulates.  So when he
turns 13 years old, he has 60,000 left
unclaimed.  60,000 was added again
plus what was earned
which is the accumulation rate.  ' He
left it in the policy and didn't take it,
he still earned interest.  Then when
he turns 24 there are 927,000.
He turned 18 years old and
had 403,000.
If the client takes the 403,000,
another 60,000 will be generated.  So this is 18,000 that will
enroll in college by that year
.  Tuition
fees are required.  So this is ready to use, right?
He can get pregnant.  Plus the
dividends.  The total dividends if
not taken are 143.
Can you take the same?  Yes,
you can, or you just want one.  It's up to
you.
If you take that, another
60,000 will be given.  As for dividends,
another dividend will be given again.  So
total living benefit.  This is the
biggest benefit.  All the money that came in
, all the money that was earned, it's all here
.  So when he turns 30 years
old, he has 3.8 million.  When
the client wanted it, he thought, what
if I withdraw this total living
benefit?  The
plan will be terminated.  What a waste, isn't it?  Why
withdraw?  Well, you can enjoy
the best benefits of the plan because
you won't be paying anything by that year,
right?  So you can take these
accumulated payouts, right?  All
the payouts that you haven't taken at the
age of 30 1.6 6, take it or
you want to include dividends so
almost 2 million, take it, there's
another 60,000 that will be generated again and
another dividends will be given again, so that
means all the money that comes in or
goes out of here will be given away,
all that money if you leave it, it will earn, okay,
so what's the purpose of it? You can
use it as a retirement fund, first use it as your
child's educational fund,
your child won't be in school forever, and
after that, use it as a retirement
fund because it will last until 100 years old, right?
So there are
many purposes.
After 6 years,
when the 60,000 comes out,
you can also use it as a help or
supplement, additional, what is
additional for the premium payment,
right? So 163, you have 160, only 103
annually until you finish the installment,
but the beauty of this plan is that even if
you haven't finished the installment, you have
an amount to enjoy.  Okay?  And then
total death benefit
2,915.
If you notice, the amount is also getting bigger and
bigger.  Because if ever
all the total money that came out of this
is already accumulated, the client didn't take it
, something will happen.
Also, Sunlife will just add that to the
client's total life insurance coverage.
That's what the beneficiaries will get.
So what else?  You can turn this into a
travel fund, a birthday fund, it's up to
you because you'll receive it every year
.  Okay?  It's like you're already doing business just by being there
.  No, you don't
need any staff
or anything.  He's just there on
paper, right?  You just accept.  So
this is Sunlife Secure Income 15.
It has a minimum amount if it
goes too high above 1 million and
the premium is not affordable.  We can reduce it
to a minimum.  But of course, if
the face amount is changed, the
guaranteed payout amount will also change because
the 6% will always be based on the face amount.
So there he is.  So this is one of the
best plans of sunlife.  There you go.
That's it.